let questions=[
    {
        numb:1,
        question:'The robot is?',
        answer: 'All of the above',
        options:[
            'Is very primitive at the present',
            'Represents the most powerful new industrial automation',
            'Will be more useful when robot version is improved',
            'All of the above'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:2,
        question:'The end effector of a robot is',
        answer: 'All of the above',
        options:[
            'Can to actual tool',
            'Many have a gripping action',
            'Is a robot hand',
            'All of the above'
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:3,
        question:'Robotic manipulator are mostly used in ',
        answer:'Electric motor actuator',
        options:[
            'Hydraulic actuator',
            'Pneumatic actuator',
            'Electric motor actuator',
            'None of the above',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:4,
        question:'End effector is also called as',
        answer:'Gripper',
        options:[
            'Gripper',
            'Tool',
            'actuator',
            'joints',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:5,
        question:'The drive which uses fluid',
        answer:'Hydraulic drive system',
        options:[
            'Electric drive system',
            'Hydraulic drive system',
            'Pneumatic drive system',
            'None of the above',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:6,
        question:'Telescopic arm is used in',
        answer:'Polar configuration',
        options:[
            'Jointed arm configuration',
            'Cartesian configuration',
            'Polar configuration',
            'Cylindrical cinfiguration',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:7,
        question:'Which of the following is not an advantage of robotics',
        answer:'Time consuming',
        options:[
            'Efficient',
            'No fatigue',
            'Speed',
            'Time consuming',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:8,
        question:'Which type of gripper used for ferrous objects',
        answer:'Magnetic Gripper',
        options:[
            'Vaccum Gripper',
            'Mechanical Gripper',
            'Magnetic Gripper',
            'Adhesive Gripper',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:9,
        question:'Which type of Gripper uses negative air pressure',
        answer:'Vaccum Gripper',
        options:[
            'Vaccum Gripper',
            'Mechanical Gripper',
            'Magnetic Gripper',
            'Adhesive Gripper',
        ]
    },

    {
        numb:10,
        question:'Which of following can be used as a sensor in robot',
        answer:'Thermometer',
        options:[
            'brake',
            'clutch',
            'Resistor',
            'Thermometer',
        ]
    },
];
